<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Providing Water</string>

    <string name="credits">Anders Lunde \n Morten Alver Normann \n Thea Hove Johansen \n Andreas Malmgård \n Marcus Nickelsen \n Anna Karina Magnussen</string>

    <!-- Strings that must not change-->
    <string name="profile_preferences">com.magicaeludos.profile</string>
    <string name="firstTime">com.magicaeludos.firstTime</string>
    <string name="totalWater">com.magicaeludos.totalWater</string>
    <string name="upgradeNr1">com.magicaeludos.upgrade1</string>
    <string name="upgradeNr2">com.magicaeludos.upgrade2</string>
    <string name="mostCollectedWaterInOneRun">com.magicaeludos.mostCollectedWaterInOneRun</string>
    <string name="mostGainedWaterInOneRun">com.magicaeludos.mostGainedWaterInOneRun</string>
    <string name="totalAmountOfRuns">com.magicaeludos.totalAmountOfRuns</string>
    <string name="villages">com.magicaeludos.villagers</string>
    <string name="currentDay">com.magicaeludos.currentDay</string>
    <string name="runsLeftToday">com.magicaeludos.runsLeftToday</string>

    <string name="level">level</string>

    <!-- Level spesific strings-->
    <string name="level_info_1">
        A person needs at least 20L of water every day for drinking and other needs. Pick up water and avoid obstacles to not spoil it! \n Swipe the screen to move!
    </string>
    <string name="level_info_2">
        10% of all people is forced to rely on contaminated water sources for basic needs. Walk over brown puddles to pick up dirty water and filtrate it at the end!
    </string>
    <string name="level_info_3">
        Water access becomes more difficult every year because of overconsumption. With increasing level of difficulty, more water is gathered for each drop or puddle.
    </string>
    <string name="level_info_4">
        In Ethiopia, women walk up to 6 hours to collect water, but sometimes the water needs to be gathered in a hurry. Run your way home!
    </string>


    <!-- Strings containing information about water-->
    <string name="water_info_0">
        "800 children under five years of age die every day from diarrhea due to lack of safe water, sanitation and basic hygiene."
    </string>
    <string name="water_info_1">
        "According to the UN, the required amount of water to ensure basic human needs such as drinking, cooking and cleaning is 20 – 50 litres per person each day. A Norwegian citizen uses on average 200 litres of water per day. That is 20 times the daily usage of a villager in Kenya."
    </string>
    <string name="water_info_2">
        "Polluted water is one of the main causes of human disease, and the problem is most severe in poor areas. Typhoid fever, cholera, diphtheria, diarrhoea and hepatitis are examples of diseases that are transmitted through polluted drinking water."
    </string>
    <string name="water_info_3">
        "Clean drinking water is part of the UN’s sustainable development goals and reads: “Ensure access to water and sanitation for all.” This goal exists because of the fact that millions of people die each year of diseases due to the lack of access to clean drinking water and good sanitation. Most of these people are children."
    </string>
    <string name="water_info_4">
        "In 1992, the UN General Assembly decided that the 22nd of March should be the World Water Day. Every year, UN Water (the unit coordinating UN related work on water and sanitation) decide on a new theme for the World Water Day. In 2016, the theme was “Water and Jobs.”"
    </string>

    <!-- Strings containing information source-->
    <string name="water_info_source_0">
        "Source: UNICEF (blogs.unicef.org)"
    </string>
    <string name="water_info_source_1">
        "Source: UNICEF (unicef.no/rent-vann-sanitaer)"
    </string>
    <string name="water_info_source_2">
        "Source: United Nations (fn.no/Tema/Vann)"
    </string>
     <string name="water_info_source_3">
        "Source: United Nations (fn.no/Tema/Vann)"
    </string>
     <string name="water_info_source_4">
        "Source: United Nations (fn.no/Tema/Vann)"
    </string>
</resources>
